{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian5.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro hanno voglio di un caffe",
                "loro hanno voglia di un caffe"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro hanno voglia di un caffe'.",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517336829.0112815,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They feel like having a coffee.\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere voglia di",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517336753.2638674,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to feel like something\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lei ha bisogno di una sciarpa",
                "lei ha bisogno di una sciarpa"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei ha bisogno di una sciarpa.",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1517336796.6144738,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She needs a scarf.\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "panino",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517336723.4038043,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sandwich\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ecco i miei amici",
                "Ecco i miei amici"
            ],
            "answer": "Ecco i miei amici.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517336757.6478634,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Here are my friends.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Giorgio e Pete hanno sempre sonno"
            ],
            "answer": "Giorgio e Pete hanno sempre sonno.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517336786.8031058,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Giorgio and Pete are always sleepy.\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Betty e Rose hanno sempre fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Betty e Rose hanno sempre fretta.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336683.51636,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Betty and Rose are always in a hurry.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Io e Kate abbiamo sempre caldo"
            ],
            "answer": "Io e Kate abbiamo sempre caldo.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336608.1522026,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Kate and I are always hot.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they feel like a coffee",
                "they feel like having a coffee",
                "They feel like having a coffee"
            ],
            "answer": "They feel like having a coffee.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517336913.1266608,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro hanno voglia di un caffe'.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "she needs a scarf",
                "She needs a scarf"
            ],
            "answer": "She needs a scarf.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336890.8593762,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lei ha bisogno di una sciarpa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Here are my friends"
            ],
            "answer": "Here are my friends.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336855.9190028,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ecco i miei amici.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "studentesse",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336895.98536,
            "question": "Plural of studentessa",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cugine",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336915.6224728,
            "question": "Io ho una cugina -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to feel like"
            ],
            "answer": "to feel like something",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336845.7909865,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere voglia di\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "noi abbiamo bisogno di un ventilatore",
                "abbiamo bisogno di un ventilatore"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi abbiamo bisogno di un ventilatore.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336937.9626286,
            "question": "Given the definition \"We need a fan.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "male student",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336918.7030666,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"studente\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sciarpa",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336967.1210077,
            "question": "Given the definition \"scarf\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "friends",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336973.346318,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"amici\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Giorgio and Pete are always sleepy",
                "Giorgio and Pete are always tired"
            ],
            "answer": "Giorgio and Pete are always sleepy.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336990.762012,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Giorgio e Pete hanno sempre sonno.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Marie ha sempre freddo",
                "Maria ha sempre freddo"
            ],
            "answer": "Maria ha sempre freddo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336982.5464709,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Maria is always cold.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "figli",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517336945.2264204,
            "question": "Io ho un figlio -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "amico",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517336984.9547002,
            "question": "Given the definition \"male friend\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ventilatore",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517336970.9741077,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fan\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hai",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517336949.6945336,
            "question": "Tu ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Matteo is always hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "Matteo is always hungry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337014.654332,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Metteo ha sempre fame.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337004.718158,
            "question": "Lei ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fan",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337001.5581791,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ventilatore\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sorelle",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337020.3100822,
            "question": "Io ho una sorella -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Anche, io ho sempre fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Anche io ho sempre fretta.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517336999.4220455,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I am always in a hurry, too.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337023.9738007,
            "question": "Voi ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ragazze",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337008.766442,
            "question": "Plural of ragazza",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "zie",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337017.350111,
            "question": "Io ho una zia -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Maria is always cold"
            ],
            "answer": "Maria is always cold.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337028.4583662,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Maria ha sempre freddo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "male friend",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337045.8700151,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"amico\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "female student",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337053.6858654,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"studentessa\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There are four boys and five girls",
                "There are four boys and 5 girls"
            ],
            "answer": "There are four boys and five girls.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337040.3225715,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci sono quattro ragazzi e cinque ragazze.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "studentessa",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337050.7259207,
            "question": "Given the definition \"female student\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scarf",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337047.861974,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sciarpa\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "amici",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337065.7575157,
            "question": "Given the definition \"friends\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Lui ha voglio di un panino",
                "Lui ha voglia di un panino"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui ha voglia di un panino.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337064.0061958,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He feels like having a sandwich.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "abbiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337070.4176211,
            "question": "(avere) noi ->",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "coffee",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337068.145763,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"caffe'\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Kate and I are always hot",
                "Kate and me are always hot"
            ],
            "answer": "Kate and I are always hot.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337082.1478608,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io e Kate abbiamo sempre caldo.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to need",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337074.6977706,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere bisogno di\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nipoti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517337103.8138247,
            "question": "Io ho una nipote -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bambini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337084.641735,
            "question": "Io ho un bambino -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "studenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337088.3297174,
            "question": "Plural of studente",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "abbiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337099.8055422,
            "question": "Noi ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Betty and Rose are always in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "Betty and Rose are always in a hurry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337128.5051455,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Betty e Rose hanno sempre fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hanno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337145.4574296,
            "question": "(avere) loro ->",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "uno studente"
            ],
            "answer": "studente",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337132.6976337,
            "question": "Given the definition \"male student\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am always in a hurry, also",
                "I am also always in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "I am always in a hurry, too.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337142.9857368,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Anche io ho sempre fretta.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sorelle",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337108.8458164,
            "question": "Plural of sorella",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337130.4498217,
            "question": "(avere) voi ->",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337106.157702,
            "question": "Lui ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Ci sono quattro ragazzi e cinque ragazze"
            ],
            "answer": "Ci sono quattro ragazzi e cinque ragazze.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337121.7537303,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There are four boys and five girls.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337147.7094812,
            "question": "Marta ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "amica",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337158.3331995,
            "question": "Given the definition \"female friend\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hanno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337163.3494043,
            "question": "Loro ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ragazzi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337155.8934956,
            "question": "Plural of ragazzo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fratelli",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337177.769166,
            "question": "Plural of fratello",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "female friend",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337175.0171869,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"amica\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "caffe"
            ],
            "answer": "caffe'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517337179.969351,
            "question": "Given the definition \"coffee\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "He feels like having a sandwich"
            ],
            "answer": "He feels like having a sandwich.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337170.993531,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui ha voglia di un panino.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337184.2253568,
            "question": "(avere) lui/lei/Lei ->",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337198.9174237,
            "question": "Carlo ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "padri",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337191.6731834,
            "question": "Plural of padre",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sandwich",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337182.321227,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"panino\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nonne",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337203.64518,
            "question": "Io ho una nonna -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere bisogno di",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337208.3650935,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to need\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bambine",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517337213.3248162,
            "question": "Io ho una bamina -> Io ho due ___",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "We need a fan"
            ],
            "answer": "We need a fan.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337196.587471,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Noi abbiamo bisogno di un ventilatore.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ho",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337231.888686,
            "question": "(avere) io ->",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hai",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337230.1693609,
            "question": "(avere) tu ->",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "madri",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337228.4798074,
            "question": "Plural of madre",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Matteo ha sempre fame"
            ],
            "answer": "Metteo ha sempre fame.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337221.525234,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Matteo is always hungry.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ho",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517337224.4211335,
            "question": "Io ___ due sorelle.",
            "tried": 4
        }
    ]
}